McConnell, John W., Papers /3052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General Account: Estimated, 1954-1956 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Principal Features of the Hughes-Ashbery. Bill and Estimated Effects of the Financing Provisions (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Management and Unions Look Ahead / E. Wight Bakke (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Interstate Conf. of Employment Security Agencies, 1950-1951 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Adequacy of Benefits Under Unemployment Insurance, 1937-1952 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Conference on Unvi. Educ. And Student Life, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Economic Security Act - Hearings (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Economic Security Act - Hearings (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Economic Security Act - Hearings (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Records of books McConnell requested to have purchased by the Univ. (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Unemployment Insurance Tax Rates, 1952-1955 (Box 54.1, Folder 1)
- A "Freedom Budget" for all Americans, 1966 (Box 54.1, Folder 2)
- Tobacco Industry, 1969 (Box 54.1, Folder 3)
- Tobacco Industry [cont.], 1969 (Box 54.1, Folder 4)
- Beals McCarthy & Rogers (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Ithaca Gun Company (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Allen-Wales (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Wales-Strippett Corporation (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Joseph E. Bright - Employee-Employee Security Plan (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Allen-Wales Statistics (Box 55, Folder 6)
- GLF Pension Plan (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Whitmer-Jackson Company (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Outlines (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Allen-Wales - Pension Plan (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Brochl, W.G. Jr. (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Electro-Refractories & Alloys Corp. (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Buffalo Study (tables) (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Curtis Screw Company (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Buffalo Steel Company (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Oliver Gear & machine Company (Box 55, Folder 16)
- R.C. Neal Company (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Worthington Pump (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Buffalo (Box 55, Folder 19)
- GLF Pension Plan (Box 55, Folder 20)
- GLF - Sabo, Lad (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Ithaca Gun Company (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Morse Chain Copies (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Mr. Chamberlain, Agent in Charge, Pension Trusts (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Buffalo Chamber of Commerce - Mr. Albert W. Dold, Industrial Relations, Secretary, Ind. Rel. Dept. (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Herbert G. Vogt - Retirement Plans, Inc. (Box 55.1, Folder 1)
- Morse Chain (Box 55.1, Folder 2)
- Allen Wales Adding Machine Div. - Retirement Plans (Box 55.1, Folder 3)
- Allen-Wales (Box 55.1, Folder 4)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Miscellaneous Professions (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Survey of Retired Employees - N.Y. State Teachers (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Survey of Retired Employees - N.Y. State Teachers [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Survey of Retired Employees - N.Y. State Teachers [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Survey of Retired Employees - N.Y. State Teachers [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Misc. Professions (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Electric [cont.] (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Westinghouse Electric Corporation (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Westinghouse Electric Corporation (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Westinghouse Electric Corporation (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Survey of Retired Employees - International Harvester Company (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Survey of Retired Employees - International Harvester Company (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Survey of Retired Employees - B.F. Goodrich Rubber Company (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Survey of Retired Employees - General Foods (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Johnson + Johnson (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Johnson + Johnson (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Atlanta Refining Company (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Otis Elevator Company (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Caterpillar Tractor Company (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Carrier Corp. (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Eli Lilly & Company (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Inland Steel Company (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Packard Motor Company (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Packard Motor Company (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Packard Motor Company (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Packard Motor Company (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Not coded or tabulated (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Not coded or tabulated (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Consolidated Edison (N.Y.) Company (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Consolidated Edison (N.Y.) Company (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Survey of Retired Employees - Consolidated Edison (N.Y.) Company (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Social Security Study - R. Risley (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Social Security Study - R. Risley (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Names & Addresses of Interviewees (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Questionnaires Returned / incorrect addresses (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Adams, Leonard (Box 59, Folder 1)
- News Releases (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Seminar ILR and Others (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Social Action Notes for Priests - Sel. Red. (Box 59, Folder 4)
- State Programs - Form 2 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Coghill, Mary Ann (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Eagan, Frances P. (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Mrs. Dorothea S. Fisher (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Leah, Almina (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Straus, Lucy (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Student Personnel Information (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Library Acquisitions - 1956 Forward (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Library Acquisitions - 1956 Forward (Box 59, Folder 13)
- NYS Reorganization Plan (DofL) (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Recommendations (other than staff) (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Sabbatic Leaves (Box 60, Folder 3)
- School Announcement Material, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Secondary School Program (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Faculty Minutes - Sept. 1958 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Faculty - Annual Meetings (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Faculty - Legislation (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Faculty - Program Planning Sessions (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Faculty - Graduate (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Faculty - Information (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Faculty - books ordered for (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Faculty - Committee Assignments (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Faculty - Full Professors (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Graduate Assistantships (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Graduate Students Fall, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Index of Business Activity in NY State (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Faculty - Salaries (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Faculty - Teaching Assignment (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Joint Legislative Com. On ILR Cond. (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Faculty - Manuscript Review (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Faculty - Members (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Faculty - Minutes (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Faculty - Minutes (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Faculty - Minutes (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Faculty - Personnel Policy (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Labor Management Conferences (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Guide to LMDC - ILR Library (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Labor-Management Conference, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Report - Univ. Library, 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Meeting of Directors (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Mexican Educators (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Foreign Visitors to the school (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Freshmen Advisees, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Freshman Convocation (Box 62, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR - School Information (Box 62, Folder 6)
- IRRA Meetings (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Job Applicants, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- ILR - Training/Education Correspondence (Box 62, Folder 9)
- ILR - Training/Education Correspondence (Box 62, Folder 10)